Guide to the World Student Christian Federation Europe Region Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Administrative and Fundraising Records
  - Project funding
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - WCC, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - 9.4 Correspondence, applications - U.S and European churches, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - 9.4 9.4 Correspondence, applications, 1997-1999 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing correspondence
    - 9.5 Office correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - 9.5 Office correspondence, 1990 Jan-Feb (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - 9.5 Office correspondence, 1990 Feb-Mar (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - 9.5 Office correspondence, 1990 Mar (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - 9.5 Office correspondence, 1990 Mar-May (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - 9.5 Office correspondence, 1990 May-Jun (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - 9.5 Office correspondence, 1990 Jun-Aug (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - 9.5 Office correspondence, 1990 Aug-Dec (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising / donor reports
    - 9.6 Fundraising guidelines, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - 9.6 European Youth Foundation, 1983, 1990-1992 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - 9.6 European Youth Foundation, 1989-1992 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - 9.6 European Youth Foundation, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - 9.6 European Youth Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - 9.6 European Youth Foundation, 1993--1994 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - 9.6 European Youth Foundation, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - 9.6 European Youth Foundation, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - 9.6 European Youth Centre, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - 9.6 Grant applications/ contracts - European Commission, Youth for Europe, 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Received and outgoing correspondence
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - 9.7 Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Administrative correspondence
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - 9.8 Letter copies, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - 9.9 Letter copies, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - 9.10 Letter copies, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - 9.10 Letter copies, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - 9.10 Letter copies, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - 9.10 Letter copies, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - 9.10 Letter copies, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - 9.10 Letter copies, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - 9.10 Letter copies, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - 9.10 Letter copies, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - 9.11 Letter copies, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - 9.11 Letter copies, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - 9.11 Letter copies, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - 9.11 Letter copies, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - 9.11 Letter copies, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - 9.11 Letter copies, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - 9.11 Letter copies, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - 9.11 Letter copies, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - 9.12 Regional Secretary correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - 9.12 Regional Secretary correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - 9.12 North South Centre WCRP United correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - 9.12 Letters, meetings, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - 9.12 Letters, meetings, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - 9.12 Mailouts, 1998-1999 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - 9.12 ECB correspondence/membership, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - 9.12 ECB correspondence/membership, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - 9.12 ECB correspondence/membership, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Related Organizations
  - European Student Chaplains' Conference
    - 10.1 Meeting documents, 1970, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - 10.1 Meeting documents, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - 10.1 Meeting documents, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - 10.1 Meeting documents, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - 10.1 Meeting documents, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - 10.2 Meeting documents, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - 10.3 Financial documentation, 1987-1990 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - 10.3 Meeting documents, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - 10.3 Meeting documents, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - 10.3 Discussion of future of ESCC, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - 10.3 Financial meeting, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - 10.3 Meeting documents, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 10.3 Meeting documents, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - 10.3 Meeting documents, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - 10.3 Meeting documents, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - American chaplains groups
    - Newsletters of Campus Ministry Women and National Campus Ministry Association, 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical Forum of European Christian Women
    - Constitution, minutes, correspondence, Third Assembly report, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, correspondence, reports, 1992-1993 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, correspondence, report from Fourth Assembly, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Addendum 2017, Series X
  - Movement correspondence
    - By country / region
      - Austria, 1980-1990 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Belgium, 1980-1982 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Belgium, 1983-1989 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Bulgaria, 1982-1991 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1981-1989 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1990-1991 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Denmark, 1980-1984 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Denmark, 1985-1995 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - East Europe, 1989-1991 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - East Timor, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Finland, 1979-1984 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Finland, 1984-1991 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - France (FFACE), 1982-1988 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - France (Centre Vaugirard), 1984-1988 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - France, 1974-1982 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - France, 1988-1994 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Germany, 1979-1986 (Box 72, Folder 5-6)
      - Germany (East and West), 1985-1988 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Germany (East and West), 1985-1990 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Great Britain, Ireland, 1979-1984 (Box 73, Folder 3-5)
      - Great Britain, Ireland, 1979-1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Great Britain, Ireland, 1985-1990 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Greece, 1980-1990 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Guatemala, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Hungary, 1979-1991 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Italy, 1979-1982 (Box 74, Folder 3-4)
      - Italy, 1983-1987 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Italy, 1988-1993 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Latvia, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Netherlands, 1980-1984 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Netherlands, 1984-1988 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Netherlands, 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Nordic Countries, 1984-1995 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Norway, 1980-1984 (Box 75, Folder 2-3)
      - Norway, 1984-1991 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Poland, 1980-1989 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Poland, 1989-1996 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Portugal, 1980-1986 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Portugal, 1987-1996 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Romania, 1980-1991 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Spain, 1980-1982 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Spain, 1983-1996 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Sweden, 1980-1984 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Sweden, 1984-1991 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Switzerland, 1980-1983 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Switzerland, 1983-1990 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Ukraine, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - USSR (Russia), 1980-1991 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Yugoslavia, 1979-1991 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Mixed movement correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Mixed movement correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Mixed movement correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Mixed movement correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Mixed movement correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 77, Folder 5-6)
  - Partners correspondence
    - Including re. Lingua Franca program; Student Christian Movement of Ireland; Conference of European Churches; Christian Student Club-Veliko Turnovo, Bulgaria, 1985-2009 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      Scope and Contents
      Take note that there is overlap between the sub-series. See additional material re. Lingua Franca in sub-series 4. and additional material re. student Christian movements in sub-series 1.
    - Christian Student Club-Veliko Turnovo, Bulgaria; Conference of European Churches; Evangelical Student Movement in Germany (ESG); Nordic-Baltic Cooperation Council, 1990-2010 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Council of European National Youth Committees (CENYC)/European Coordination Bureau of International Youth Organizations (ECB)/European Youth Forum (EYF), 1995-1996 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - CENYC/ECB/EYF; North-South Centre, 1995-2002 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - CENYC/ECB/EYF; Education, Audiovisual and Culture Executive Agency, 1995-2007 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - CENYC/ECB/EYF; North-South Centre, 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - European Youth Forum, 1997-2005 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - WSCF-Europe Regional Assembly; Conference of European Churches; Student Christian Movement of Canada; European Youth Forum; Lingua Franca; WSCF: Geneva Centennial Fund, 1997-2011 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - WSCF-Europe; Syndesmos; WSCF-Canada; Middle East Region WSCF; Eastern Europe Language and Leadership Training Project; ESG, 1997-2012 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - European Contact Group on Urban Industrial Mission, 1999-2001 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - WSCF; Church of Sweden, 1999-2003 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Ecumenical Youth Council in Europe, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Netherlands Missionary Council, 2001-2003 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Syndesmos World Fellowship of Orthodox Youth, 2001-2003 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Through Ecumenical Action-More Sharing, 2001-2003 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - European Commission: Directorate-General for Education and Culture, 2002-2005 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - European Commission: Directorate-General for Education and Culture; Netherlandse Zendingsraad, 2003-2005 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - WSCF-Europe; European Commission: Directorate-General for Education and Culture, 2004-2005 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Norwegian Student Christian Movement; WSCF-Europe; ESG; Conference of European Churches; WSCF-Interregional Office, 2005-2009 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Reports and documents
    - Movement reports
      - European movement reports, 1969-1982 (Box 79, Folder 1-4)
      - European movement reports, including re. Theological Commission meeting in Darmstadt (1977), 1977-1982 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Mixed movement documents: Incl. Kairos Europa; International Youth and Student Movement for the United Nations; WSCF-The Hardanger Months; African Summer School, 1984-1991 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Romanian Christian Orthodox Student Association; European Christian Environmental Network; Ecumenical Council of Churches in the Czechoslovak Socialist Republic, 1987-2000 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - WSCF-Europe and Inter-Regional Office; Student Christian Movement in Norway; Evangelical Student Movement in Germany (ESG), 1994-2004 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Saints' Methodius and Cyril Christian Educational Center-Minsk; WSCF-Europe; Student Christian Movement Evaluation Forms, 2001-2003 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Conference reports
      - Including: WSCF Conference Blank Documents; Report of the WSCF Europe Secretary to the WSCF Executive Committee; "Is Violence Ever an Answer?" Conference, 1993-2002 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Including: "Stripping Culture of 'Black and White'" Conference; Europe KAIROS Document; "Is Violence Ever an Answer?" Conference, 1993-2003 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Including: "Gender: Transition or Backlash?" Conference; "Celebrating Diversity-Diversity in Culture and Spirituality" Conference; "Is Violence Ever an Answer?" Conference, 2000-2002 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Including: "Globalization and Spirituality" Conference; "One Creation, Our Destruction, Whose Redemption?" Conference; "Celebrating Diversity-Diversity in Culture and Spirituality" Conference, 2000-2002 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Including: "Stripping Culture of 'Black and White' Thinking" Conference; Youth Pre-Consultation; WSCF-Europe Move to Oslo, 2001-2003 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - European Commission documents
      - Including: Grant Agreement #2005-0274/001-001; Grant Agreement #1999-1187/001-001; Vademecum Sulla Gestione Delle Sovvenzioni, 1997-2007 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Including: Documents Relating to Grant A-3029: "Support for international non-governmental youth organisations"; WSCF-Europe By-Laws; WSCF Constitution, 1999-2001 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Including: Documents Relating to Grant A-3029; Grant Agreement #2001-1500/001-001; Grant Agreement 2000-0717/001-001, 2000-2002 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Including: Documents Relating to Grant A-3029; Grant Agreement #2002-1393/001-001; Grant Agreement #2005-0274/001-001, 2000-2005 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Including: Documents Relating to Grant A-3029; Grant DG EAC 51/05; WSCF-Europe Narrative Report 2004, 2004-2006 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - ERA documents
      - Including: "Violence Against Women—Short Training Courses"; "Stripping Culture of 'Black and White' Thinking" Conference; Lingua Franca, 1996-2005 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Including: European Youth Forum Grant 87C; "The Contribution of Roma and Sinti Peoples to Contemporary Culture" Conference; "Women and Men Created in God's Image-But?" Conference, 1998-2003 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Including: Council of Europe Advisory Council; "Analysis of the Root Causes of Migration in Europe From Socio-Cultural, Psychological and Theological Perspectives" Conference; WSCF Europe Activities Report, 1999-2001 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Including: Youth Work in Bosnia and Herzegovina; Lingua Franca; "I Was a Stranger and You Invited Me In: Homelessness and Poverty Housing in Europe Today" Conference, 1999-2005 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Including: "Higher Education in Europe: Universities as Service Stations or Laboratories of Universal Questions?" Conference; Council of Europe Grant #87C; European Youth Forum, 2000-2005 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - European Commission and Council of Europe documents
      - Habitat for Humanity International: "Selected Data on Poverty Housing in Europe and Central Asia" Paper, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Including: Grant Agreement #2007-0161/001-001; "WSCF and Higher Education Issues" excerpts; Solidarity Conference, 2005-2007 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Including: Youth in Action-Action 4.1 Documents; WSCF Europe Budget; Grant Agreement #2005-0274/001-001, 2006-2007 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Includes: Grant Agreement #2006-0568/001-001; Grant Agreement 2008-1001/001-001; Youth in Action-Action 4.1 documents, 2006-2008 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Including: "Family: Expectations and Exceptions?" Conference; "Europe, Art and Spirituality-Building Up Intercultural Identity" Conference; "Religion, Ethics, and Politics-god and the Use of Power" Conference, 2007-2009 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Education, Audiovisual and Culture Executive Agency 20/07 Proposals; Youth in Action-Action 4.1 Partnership Agreement #2008-1001/001-001 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Partners documents and events reports
      - Including: Lingua Franca; EELLTP; Inter-Faith Intensive English and Peace Studies Grant Application; WSCF Europe Administrative Assistant Contract, 1991-2005 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Including: EELTP; Lingua Franca; Solidarity Conference; Gathering of Senior Friends of WSCF, 1993-2008 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - EELLTP; Lingua Franca; WSCF Seminar: "May Their Voices Never Be Silenced", 1996-2006 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Including: WSCF Centennial Fund; Budapest Property Documents; WSCF Officers and Staff Meeting; Gathering of Senior Friends of WSCF, 1997-2008 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - WSCF Europe Regional Committee Meeting Minutes, Reports, 1992-2002 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Including: WSCF Europe Regional Committee Meeting Minutes; WSCF Executive Committee Meeting Minutes; Africa Regional Report; Asia Pacific Regional Report, 1999-2003 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Including: WSCF Europe Regional Committee Meeting Minutes, Reports, Evaluations; Ecumenical Assistance Program; WSCF Officers and Staff Meeting, 1999-2009 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Including: Latin America and the Caribbean Region Report to WSCF Executive Committee; Middle East Region Report to WSCF Executive Committee; Report on WSCF General Assembly, 2000-2009 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Including: WSCF Staff and Officers Meetings; World Council of Churches; Conference of European Churches; European Regional Committee Meeting, 2004-2007 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Including: European Youth Forum; WSCF Officers and Staff Meeting; Stewards Program: "Transforming Empire: Prophesy in Action", 2007-2009 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Events documents and activities reports
      - Including: "Religion, Ethics, and Politics—God and the Use of Power" Conference; Contact Lists for WSCF-Europe office and WSCF-Europe conferences, 1991-2010 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Including: Lingua Franca; EELLTP; "The Holocaust in Three Generations," ed. Gabriele Rosenthal; Youth for Europe Programme, 1996-1999 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Lingua Franca; Brot fur die Welt and Evangelischer Entwicklungsdienst; EELLTP; World Council of Churches, 1996-2011 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Lingua Franca; International English Training Course for Church Workers; European Youth Centre Language Courses for Youth Leaders; EELLTP, 1997-1998 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - WSCF Europe narrative reports on activities, 2000-2004 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - "A Just Life or Just Life?" Solidarity Conference; Theology Conference Excursion; "Discover Sikhi-Visiting a Gurdwara" article, 2008 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - "Living Our Faith in a Multicultural Society: Developing Intercultural Dialogue as a Life-Style" conference evaluations, 2008 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - "Religion, Ethics, and Politics—God and the Use of Power" conference, 2009-2010 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - "Religion, Ethics, and Politics—God and the Use of Power" conference, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Europe Language and Leadership Training Project (EELLTP /Lingua Franca program
    - Correspondence and documents, 1992-1998 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and documents, 1995-2002 (Box 83, Folder 6-8)
    - Correspondence and documents, including Greek Student Christian Movement Report, 1995-2003 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and documents, 1996-1999 (Box 83, Folder 10-13)
    - Correspondence and documents, 1996-2001 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and documents, 1997-2011 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and documents, 1998-2010 (Box 84, Folder 3-6)
    - Correspondence and documents, 1999-2008 (Box 84, Folder 7-13)
    - Correspondence and documents, 1999-2008 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and documents, 2000-2011 (Box 85, Folder 2-9)
    - Correspondence and documents, 2008-2009 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous WSCF documentation
    - Including: "The Orthodox in the WSCF: 1895-1972" Report; WSCF Europe Lists of Activities; "WSCF 100 Years On" Report, 1972-2003 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Including: International Summer Course for Youth Leaders; EELLTP; Lingua Franca, 1996-2002 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - WSCF European Regional Assembly Documents, 1997-2001 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Including: WSCF Policy Papers, By-Laws, Job Descriptions; European Regional Assembly Documents; WSCF General Assembly, 1997-2004 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Including: Diakonie; Finn Church Aid; Kerk in Actie; Conference of European Churches, 1997-2013 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Including: "Women and Partnership in the WSCF" Paper; "Women Doing Theology" Paper; Africa Region Report to WSCF Executive Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Including: WSCF Constitution; Documents related to the WSCF Europe office move from Amsterdam to Oslo; European Regional Assembly (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - WSCF General Assembly; European Regional Assembly, 1999-2008 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Including documents related to WSCF Europe office move from Amsterdam to Norway; End of WSCF Europe office stay in Norway, 2000-2010 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - European Regional Committee Meeting Minutes, 2003-2006 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - WSCF Europe Egyesulet (relating to Hungary), 2003-2012 (Box 86, Folder 11-13)
    - Including United Methodist Church International Ministries with Women, Children, and Youth; Council of Europe; Conf. of European Churches; Kerk in Actie, 2006-2012 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - WSCF Europe Egyesulet (relating to Hungary), 2004-2012 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Including Conference of European Churches; Diakonie; Kerk in Actie; World Council of Churches; Council of Europe Education, Audiovisual, and Cultural Executive Agency, 2006-2012 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - WSCF Europe Eygesulet (relating to Hungary); Lingua Franca; Brethren Volunteer Service, 2007-2012 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - WSCF Communications Committee; Centennial Fund Board; Personnel Policy and Procedures; General Assembly, 2008-2009 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - WSCF Communications Committee; Centennial Fund Board; Personnel Policy and Procedures; General Assembly, 2008-2010 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - European Youth Forum; Council of Europe Programming Committee on Youth; World Council of Churches, 2008-2011 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Conference of European Churches; Council of Europe Education, Audiovisual, and Cultural Executive Agency, 2010-2012 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Archive contact lists, 1929-1990 (Box 87, Folder 9-12)